so everyone says that the wait times for
所以每个人都说等待时间
the rides at Disney are inaccurate I'm
所以每个人都说 迪士尼的坐车等候时间是不准确的
迪士尼的骑车是不准确的
the rides at Disney are inaccurate I'm
going to put this to the test according
迪士尼的搭便车是不准确的 我要把这个测试一下
将这个放入测试
going to put this to the test according
to the Disney app there's a 65-minute
根据迪斯尼软件程序 将这个放入测试 会有65分钟
迪士尼应用程序的65分钟
to the Disney app there's a 65-minute
wait time on this ride I put on my timer
迪士尼软件的Disney App 有65分钟的等待时间 我把我的计时器放上
等待这趟旅程的等待时间 我穿上我的计时器
wait time on this ride I put on my timer
to see if this was true let's go in the
我穿上计时器 看看这是否是真的 让我们进去吧
看看这是否是真的 我们进去吧
to see if this was true let's go in the
beginning the line was moving really
看看这是否属实 让我们从开始开始 线真的在移动
开始线线真的在移动
beginning the line was moving really
slow 15 minutes in and kind of moved but
开始线的移动速度非常慢 15分钟内, 并有某种移动, 但是...
慢速的15分钟 和某种移动,但
slow 15 minutes in and kind of moved but
I don't know if we're going to make it
慢了15分钟,有点感动 但我不知道我们能不能赶得上
我不知道我们能不能成功
I don't know if we're going to make it
in time I wasn't really sitting friendly
我不知道我们能不能及时赶到 我坐的不是很友好
那时我不太友好的坐着
in time I wasn't really sitting friendly
we're about halfway through the time and
那时我不太友善 我们的时间已经过半了
我们的时间已经过半了
we're about halfway through the time and
I don't know if we're halfway through
我们的时间已经过了一半了 我不知道我们是否已经过了一半了
我不知道我们是不是已经过了一半了
I don't know if we're halfway through
the line I guess we're just going to
我不知道我们是不是已经过了一半了 我猜我们只是要去
我想我们只是要去
the line I guess we're just going to
keep moving and find out we're back
我想我们只能继续前进 发现我们回来了
继续前进,发现我们回来了
keep moving and find out we're back
outside at 38 minutes ooh what's
继续前进 发现我们三十八分钟后 回到外面
外面38分38分,哦,什么是
outside at 38 minutes ooh what's
happening am I even in line I didn't
在38分钟外的 外面的38分钟 哦 发生什么事了 我甚至排队 我没有
我连排队都没排
happening am I even in line I didn't
even think I'm in line anymore I have no
我甚至连在排队 我甚至不认为我在排队了 我没有
即使觉得我已经排在排的排在排的排在排的排在排在排的排在排在排的排在排在排在排的排在排在排在排在排的
even think I'm in line anymore I have no
idea what's going on there Storm
我甚至以为我已经排队了 我不知道那里发生了什么 暴风雨
{\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3cH2F2F2F {\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3cH2F2F2F {\fn方正黑体简体\fs18\b1\bord1\shad1\3cH2F2F2F
idea what's going on there Storm
Troopers I think we're going to beat the
我想我们会击败
士兵们,我想我们会打败
Troopers I think we're going to beat the
time we're getting really close and 46
士兵们,我想我们将会击败 我们真正接近的时候,46
时间非常接近和46
time we're getting really close and 46
minutes in and we're almost there it
时间非常接近,46分钟就到了,就快到了
几分钟内,我们就快到了
minutes in and we're almost there it
ended up only taking 50 minutes
几分钟内就到,我们快到了 最后只花了50分钟
最后只用了50分钟
ended up only taking 50 minutes
subscribe
最后最后只需要50分钟的订阅时间
本字幕由AI大模型生成